ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3063
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum
1964-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/3063
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8436552
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 09, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436552
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1964; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Forum Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 12)